{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL4.incr.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072231031","data":{"timestamp":" 948072231030"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 7a8da29e-e4a2-495f-83ee-b5d47940b8e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.102"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_m_z-e-m"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072240205","data":{"timestamp":" 948072240205"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072242795","data":{"timestamp":" 948072242795"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072244441","data":{"timestamp":" 948072244441"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072247686","data":{"timestamp":" 948072247686"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072249251","data":{"timestamp":" 948072249251"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072252131","data":{"timestamp":" 948072252130"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072253692","data":{"timestamp":" 948072253692"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072256376","data":{"timestamp":" 948072256376"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072257945","data":{"timestamp":" 948072257945"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072260141","data":{"timestamp":" 948072260140"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072260246","data":{"timestamp":" 948072260246"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" d95ff3fe-129f-43db-b520-7c584d8d1679"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072271387","data":{"timestamp":" 948072271386"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072273404","data":{"timestamp":" 948072273404"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072275014","data":{"timestamp":" 948072275014"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072277303","data":{"timestamp":" 948072277302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072278901","data":{"timestamp":" 948072278900"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072281954","data":{"timestamp":" 948072281954"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072283517","data":{"timestamp":" 948072283516"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072286283","data":{"timestamp":" 948072286283"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072287854","data":{"timestamp":" 948072287854"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072292249","data":{"timestamp":" 948072292248"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072295034","data":{"timestamp":" 948072295034"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072297712","data":{"timestamp":" 948072297712"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072299288","data":{"timestamp":" 948072299288"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072302351","data":{"timestamp":" 948072302351"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072303110","data":{"timestamp":" 948072303110"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072303918","data":{"timestamp":" 948072303918"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072312226","data":{"timestamp":" 948072312225"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072312336","data":{"timestamp":" 948072312336"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072324305","data":{"timestamp":" 948072324305"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072335177","data":{"timestamp":" 948072335177"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_042335"," gameId":" 984fd40b-2af3-4575-8cff-70f7317f0dd6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}